Quick thinking landed him a million bucks... now everybody's after it!
Blank Check is a comedy, family film directed by Rupert Wainwright.
Bullied by his siblings and nagged by his parents, 11-year-old Preston
Waters is fed up with his family — especially their frugality.
But he gets his chance to teach them a lesson when a money-laundering criminal nearly
bulldozes Preston with his car and compensates the boy with a blank check.
Preston makes the check out for $1 million and goes on
a spending spree he'll never forget.
Preston Waters, played by Brian Bonsall.
Shay Stanley, played by Karen Duffy.
Fred Waters, played by James Rebhorn.
Sandra Waters, played by Jayne Atkinson.
Ralph Waters, played by Michael Faustino.
Damian Waters, played by Chris Demetral.
Blank Check (in the United Kingdom originally released as Blank Cheque) is a 1994 American comedy film directed by Rupert Wainwright
and starring Brian Bonsall, Karen Duffy, Miguel Ferrer, James Rebhorn, Tone Lōc, Jayne Atkinson and Michael Lerner.
It was released on February 11, 1994, by Walt Disney Pictures.
The film follows a boy who inherits a blank check and uses it to buy a house under an alter ego
but is soon being searched for by several members of the bank he cashed it under.
The film received mixed-to-negative reviews and
grossed $30.8 million domestically.
The film explores themes of money laundering, stolen money,
rich kid, first crush, eccentric millionaire.
The tone is lighthearted.